Hey everyone.
Welcome to my session on deploying
Azure scenarios while sleeping.
My name is Peter Ditender.
I am a senior content developer
here at Microsoft, focusing on
AI and DevOps course material,
everything that gets published on
learn.microsoft.com, you could say.
I've been active in the
Microsoft space for 30 years.
Initially started my career a long time
ago as a physical data center person,
like literally helping with power
cabling cooling, and then you could
say throughout the years, moving up
in the stack, where it's always been
around primarily Microsoft technologies.
Server hardware, operating systems,
Exchange, SQL, moving to cloud in the
early days of Azure, and as you can
see, nowadays focusing on AI and DevOps.
If you have any questions out of this
session don't hesitate reaching out.
Email or LinkedIn connection
would be the best way.
Now, what's in it for you?
First of all, thanks for picking
my session out of that long list
of sessions you could go through.
Now, what am I gonna talk about?
I know it's an AI agent-oriented topic
for the conference, but I need to
give you a little bit of how did we do
Azure demo deployments, at least out
of my role within Microsoft, before AI.
And then in the second part, but the
biggest part of the session, I'm gonna
focus a lot more on how we apply AI
nowadays to basically still do the
same thing, but a lot more optimized
So the starting point is the challenge
of doing demos and our platform, if
you know my background a bit, being a
technical trainer at Microsoft full-time
and before that as a vendor, I needed
Azure demos for about 15 years now.
And it's targeting, I would say, towards
trainers, but I'm pretty sure if you're a
DevOps engineer, if you're a consultant,
if you're working as a cloud admin,
you probably need to show something
to your stakeholders, your customers,
your partners at some point in time.
So the platform originated for trainers,
but in meantime, we know that it's
not just being used by trainers.
Anyone who's passionate about Azure
can probably use the same logic.
Now, what makes doing and
building Azure demos challenging?
A lot of reasons, and I went through
all of these throughout my career.
First of all, there's never
enough time to create good demos.
It takes a huge amount of time
to actually build those demos.
You might deploy something in
Azure, but then a deployment doesn't
really turn it into a powerful demo.
Years ago, in the early months
and years of Azure, we had Azure
Quickstart templates in a GitHub repo.
Perfectly fine, nothing wrong
with it, but deploying something
doesn't make it a demo, right?
Or you can deploy like Azure
infrastructure, but then lacking sample
data, lacking sample applications.
Maybe you wanna showcase something
with SQL, Fabric, or any other Azure
resource, and you spin up the service,
but you don't really have data.
So anything that again fits in that
complexity of building and doing demos.
And then maybe you want to show
a demo, you build it everything
manual, and then maybe you wanna
reuse it for the next time, or you
wanna share it with your colleagues.
And again, so many other issues.
So taking this first example here as
a starter, what if you want to deploy
a virtual machine workload and maybe
adding some network specifics to it?
Sure, you can use Azure
command line interface.
You could sure deploy something from
moving around in the portal, but if
you know my background, my passion
for DevOps, meaning automation before
we called it DevOps, then preferably
rely on Azure command line interface
and then even better, maybe use
infrastructure as code, which could
be Bicep templates or Terraform.
Now, what if your workload
becomes a little bit more complex?
Like in this example here, it's
starting with a storage account,
then it adds Event Grid, functions,
AI services, Logic Apps, Cosmos DB,
Application Insight for monitoring,
and if you want even more components.
Now, what you would do here is probably,
sure, you can still rely on Azure CLI
using Bicep templates, but then you also
need to deploy application components,
like for the functions, the Event
Grid, your web application, and that's
where it might become challenging.
Or another scenario, what if you want
to duplicate or replicate that scenario
across maybe your initial development
environment, maybe across a different
development environment, from there moving
to your actual live deployment demo.
And then maybe from there you
have a customer, a partner, a
colleague who's gonna ask you
like, "Oh, that's a cool demo.
Can you share it?
Can you maybe use this as some sort
of a proof of concept?" Any of these
scenarios, easier one, maybe even more
complex ones, were the starting point
of our trainer demo deploy solution.
So what is demo deploy?
It's something that I created as a
project within Microsoft about four
years ago already, and it was…
At that time, I was part of the
technical trainer team, and obviously
with about 125 trainers at that time,
we had to do Azure demos pretty much
four hours a day, every single day
whenever we were teaching, which was
like a 90% of our day-to-day job.
So I came up with a scenario building
a web application front end, connecting
to an Azure DevOps back end, running
pipelines, allowing anyone in the team
at that moment in time, only internal
trainers, to use it as a one-click demo.
They would go to a portal, select a
scenario, click deploy, and everything
would nicely run behind the scenes.
They would use it primarily for demos,
but also using it for self-learning,
maybe using it to learn about
some new technologies that they
might need to train on later on.
Now, in short, we managed over
the last three years to get
close to 12,000 deployments,
and we have around 80 scenarios.
And as you can see, we had a
couple of different versions
from that portal as well.
Now, if you're wondering "Okay, how
does this relate to AI and agents?" I
would say hold on for now, because it's
always good to learn about the future,
but not forgetting about the present.
So I need another couple of
minutes to walk you through the
current state of the platform.
So the short link to get there is
aka.ms, that's our Microsoft short link,
and from there trainer-demo-deploy.
It's gonna get you to our portal,
where I'll walk you through a
demo in the next slide, but it's
gonna bring you to a catalog.
And then from there you can choose
any of the around 80 scenarios
that we currently have available.
Each and every scenario
comes with a title.
You can search for it.
It also links back to our
Microsoft official courseware.
You can provide feedback
on any of the scenarios.
You can actually contribute to
those as well, but I'll talk
about it all the way at the end.
And then from there you can open a
detailed scenario card Inside the scenario
card, you find a link to a GitHub profile.
So what's the setup, the topology?
Out of the Microsoft
project, we own the catalog.
We're publishing the scenarios,
but we don't really own them.
And sure, some of the VT members
within Microsoft, but also outside of
Microsoft, are heavily contributing
to this platform, but each and every
author of a scenario remains the author.
So they're not official
Microsoft templates, if that's
what you're looking for.
Keep in mind that the whole purpose
is giving you demo scenarios.
And then sure, you can
use quite a lot of them.
I think we have around 15, 20 of
them in the meantime covering AI
services with Foundry for language,
and in the short amount of time, or
the near term, we're gonna release
a few agentic scenarios as well.
For each and every scenario, so again,
you find the author GitHub profile, you
find the link to the actual scenario
repo in the individual contributor's
GitHub account, a description what the
scenario is about, and then also quite
relevant, whenever you deploy something
in cloud, you know that cost meter is
running, so we provide you an overview
of the cost estimate for about 24 hour
runtime, as well as a demo install time,
which are obviously always estimates.
Since we're focusing on doing demos
instead of just waiting for a deployment,
which typically involves just Azure
infrastructure, but then also sample
applications, if there is a sample
workload like a web app, a container,
maybe container apps, maybe Kubernetes
or functions like anything that requires
an application to really showcase
what the Azure service can provide,
that's also part of the scenario.
But then we also provide you the actual
demo guide, which means it's typically
a short overview with screenshots most
of the time, how to actually go through
the demo after The deployment itself, I
talked about the fact that years ago it
started with a DevOps backend, but right
now it's a full open source project.
Everything is GitHub repo based, and
the deployment vehicle behind the
scenes is AZD Azure Developer CLI.
So what is AZD?
I'll walk you through a demo in a minute.
But it's basically four steps,
four clicks if you want.
You're gonna initialize
the scenario AZD in it.
From there, it's gonna clone
the repo for that specific
scenario to your local machine.
You're gonna run AZD up.
That's gonna ask you an
environment variable name.
It's gonna ask you to authenticate
towards your Azure subscription.
And then depending on the scenario,
a couple of minutes, maybe about
forty-five minutes, I think, is the
most complex scenario we currently
have, and that's showing everything up
and running in your Azure environment.
So in short, four steps if you want.
Create a new folder on your local
machine, run AZD in it, run AZD up.
Scenario gets deployed.
You open the demo guide.
You can go through as a demo, but again,
you could also use it as a learning tool.
And then if you want to delete the
deployed scenario, you can rely on AZD
down, and that will nicely remove purging
any resources that you no longer need.
Enough about that in slides for
now because I literally like
showing you in a demo, and that's
what I'm gonna do from here.
So when you navigate to that short
link, aka.ms/Trainerdemodeploy,
this is like the homepage.
So I would say spend a little bit of
time like going through the homepage
to validate like what is available.
As you can see up here, we do have
the catalog that I'll obviously
walk you through in a minute.
You can bring your own deployment in your
own Azure subscriptions, and then you
could also do Copilot Studio, which I'm
not gonna cover in this session because
it's primarily around Azure deployments
and even more so using AI agents later on.
We have a section with frequently
asked questions and how to
contribute, but I'll explain that
as part of the presentation as well.
So for now, it's most important to
zoom in a little bit on the catalog.
So as mentioned in the presentation,
you can use the catalog just for
finding about AD, I mentioned, but
in meantime, between presentation and
actual platform, the list of static
templates is quite dynamic because we
have the in like a weekly maintenance
where some templates are getting taken
offline, fixing, and then pushing back,
so that's why the numbers are never exact.
You can search based on pretty much
any service, so if you're into like
Foundry, it's immediately gonna filter.
If you look for a scenario based
on keywords, like we do have that
cold boot scenario that I showed
you in I think slide number four
or five in the presentation.
And from here, you select a card and it's
gonna open the card details on the side.
So as mentioned again, you find
information about cost, a time estimate
to run the actual deployment, and if
you have application dependencies,
we typically try to give you a link.
Looks a little bit weird here, but it's
just a text document that we're opening.
So in this case, for this example, it's
specifically using .NET eight framework.
You need PowerShell seven, and you
also need the node framework for
running this specific workload.
Now, since I'm using AZD for the
deployment, the source code of
the scenario will be moved to your
local machine, and that's why you
need… if it's a container example,
you need Docker on your machine.
If it's Python, Node .NET, you
need those SDK frameworks as well.
As mentioned, we also have the demo
guide, and again, this is not written in
stone, so it's more like a suggestion.
And this is typically where we would
ask for some contribution, some help.
If you think we can do even better
different demos than what we already
described, then please let us know.
There's a link to a small side project
where we had course blueprints,
so just highlighting this scenario
could be used for a specific like
Microsoft course in preparation
for certification, for example.
And then the legal statement is just
because it's a Microsoft open source,
we are required to list that up here.
Let's go back to the template details
and running an actual deployment.
Now, this scenario takes about 12
minutes, so I'm not gonna show you
what it looks like, but let's take a
step back and showing you a little bit
more what we have to filter, although
this should be pretty straightforward.
I'm gonna use a small example,
one that I know I can deploy
in just a couple of minutes.
Now, one other feature we have
is the direct link to the source
author, this is myself in this
case, where you don't really have
to use the catalog, but obviously
we try to centralize all of them.
Now, before even running the
deployment, you could basically read
through, you can check the files
like what is getting deployed inside.
You have the demo files, the deployment
Bicep files, and everything that you need.
Cool.
Now, what is the most easy scenario
to get a deployment running?
So I'm gonna use this storage
account scenario, and I'm not
gonna remove anything, like not
editing the recording whatsoever.
I'm literally gonna
follow all these steps.
So the recommendation is to create
a new folder on your local machine.
So I'm gonna select this.
I'm gonna open my terminal
And from here, I can literally perform
like four clicks, make the directory.
The next step is move into that directory.
Inside, we're gonna run azd init, and
behind the scenes, it's gonna perform a
Git clone, like cloning this repo from
my GitHub account, this repo folder
into my local machine, and then it's
gonna ask me for an environment name.
This is an azd step where the environment
name in most of the templates we have
is being used for naming conventions.
So I'm gonna call this the pdt-storage And
now we can actually run the deployment,
and as you can see down here, it's AZD up.
So I'm gonna copy.
Obviously, no need to really copy.
You could just type it in, and it tells
me like, "Oh, there is no project."
Why not?
Because I'm not in the correct subfolder,
so I need to move one level down.
That's my mistake.
Now this is triggering
the actual deployment.
So as you can see, it's running
Bicep because it's a Bicep template.
I already pre-authenticated my
AZD session, and it's gonna ask me
where, in which Azure subscription
do you want to deploy this?
I'm gonna use my Microsoft internal
employee subscription, where next it's
gonna ask me where in all the different
Azure regions do you want to deploy.
Anything that's happening here or
happening after this step is just Azure,
which means if you have policies in
place that you cannot deploy to all
regions, if you have policies in place
where a template is deploying specific
resources, but you're not allowed to
deploy them because of SKUs, versions,
availability, whatsoever, deployment
will fail in the same way it fails if you
would not run this using the AZD setup.
It already kicked off the deployment.
So we call the scenario pdt store
for like storage and using that
environment variable, it gets
used for the resource group naming
Where then next I can see
my deployment is running.
Not all resources are there, but if
I move into settings, deployments,
I can see my ongoing deployment.
I can switch back and I can see over
here that my deployment is still running.
So I'll give it another minute
or two, and then once it's fully
deployed, I can show you what it
means to have an actual demo scenario
So after about two minutes and a
half, as you can see here, we have
successfully deployed scenario.
So let me switch back
to my Azure environment.
Obviously, deployment here
is successful as well.
Now the actual part of the demo comes
in where I do have my resources,
in this case, my storage account.
And if I go back to my scenario, open the
demo guide, I can literally follow along.
So what it shows me here is the
difference between blob storage and
file share storage, where I basically
have to follow the steps, navigate
to storage, select replication, go
to the browser, open blob containers.
So let me do that.
Storage browser, blob containers, images,
and I do have all the images here.
If you're a bit familiar with Azure, you
probably know how this works, but this
also means that like RBAC permissions for
my admin to connect to the data storage
is also part of that demo scenario.
I could then navigate to file
shares, open the file share, and
again, seeing similar images.
So that's in short how
to run the deployment.
Now, imagine I no longer
need my demo scenario.
You tested it, you validated it.
If you're a trainer, a
consultant, you did your demo.
I go back to my terminal and I'm gonna
run azd down, and that's gonna delete
the scenario from Azure, but it's keeping
the source code on my local machine.
Now from here, because again, it's
cloned to your local machine, you can
actually make your own changes and
then preferably consider contributing.
If you do azd down and then adding
purge and force, it's not gonna ask
a confirmation, and the purge is
helpful for those like soft deleted
like a Key Vault or basically any
AI service like language boundary.
All of them will get flagged with
a purge option, and that means that
you can immediately redeploy them.
Otherwise, they're like stored in a soft
delete for, I think, thirty days, and
that's not really useful, beneficial
if you wanna run this deployment again.
So after the azd down is complete…
I'm not gonna wait for it because it
sometimes takes a little bit longer.
But once the azd down is complete,
resource group is gone, you can
immediately run azd up again
the day after, a minute after,
three weeks later, and it's gonna
redeploy it in the exact same state.
So this is the first part of what
the tool is doing, but I got a little
bit more to talk about, so let's
switch back to the presentation.
Good.
So we're about 15 minutes in, and I didn't
really talk much about AI and agents.
So that's where I would say the second
part of the session might be a lot
more worthwhile for a lot of you.
But again, I don't like to talk
about the future, present and
future with AI and agents without
forgetting what we have before agents.
But the nice thing is that I can
announce it's not an official
announcement because it's been active
for a couple of months already.
But if you think about the previous
piece, it's static scenarios.
You grab a scenario, you
deploy it in Azure, and you
can repeat it over and over.
But then we got feedback from trainers,
customers, learners, partners, pretty
much anyone using the platform like
can we make our own custom demos?"
Sure you can.
First of all, again, it's an open
source scenario, so you can clone the
repo, you can clone each and every
individual scenario, but then preferably
we want you to contribute back as well.
Now, again, if you think back about
one of my first slides, like all those
challenges in doing demos, one of the
biggest challenges is coming up with the
idea, building, testing, validating the
scenario, and then making it available.
So that's where now we can
heavily use agentic approach.
So what we did is not changing anything
in the scenario concept, like we still
have Azure templates using Bicep.
We still have a demo guide, we still
have the sample applications and
data, but now we're actually providing
you with a collection of agents
in VS Code using GitHub Copilot.
So the starting point is out of those
about 80 scenarios, go out and use them.
But maybe even better, that's
where obviously the passion for
AI and agents is now coming in.
You can write a prompt and you can start
creating your own demo scenarios totally
away from the already 80 published ones.
So you can run a prompt and you can
imagine there's a demo coming up
You use all the agents that we have.
It's a step-by-step scenario, eight agents
nicely working together as a multi-agent
scenario, all driven from within GitHub
Copilot in VS Code, or if you want,
GitHub Copilot CLI, which means you
don't need Foundry, you don't need any
complex Azure backend to start using it.
From there, you open the repo
and you activate the agent.
You call the agent orchestrator, and from
there, you run a prompt, and I'll show
you again in a demo "Hey, can you build
me a demo scenario to showcase a web app
and a Cosmos database?" Just an example.
And it's gonna ask you a
couple of questions like,
how do you wanna deploy it?
Where do you wanna use it?
What kind of industry do
you wanna tailor this for?
Do you need any specifics, like
maybe integrating security best
practices, maybe high availability?
That's all part of that custom experience.
It also gonna ask you if you want
to add an application layer to it.
Depending on the resources, there's
a architecture validation based
on the Well-Architected Framework
and the Cloud Adoption Framework
best practices that we have within
Microsoft, and from there, it's gonna
create all the necessary artifacts.
A Bicep template using the
modular approach, preferably
Azure verified modules.
It's gonna rely on the
AZD deployment concept.
It creates a .NET based application,
but you could change it to Python,
Java, any other development language.
It's gonna run the test deployment if
something should not work as expected.
Out of that agentic approach, it's gonna
do a rollback, trying to fix the problem,
rolling doing the deployment again.
Once the deployment is successful, it's
gonna integrate Microsoft Playwright
user framework testing, and from
there, creating demo guides on the
fly, including screenshots and all bare
minimum demo steps you can think of.
And then last, if you are satisfied
with the scenario it created, the
deployment works, the demo is pretty
cool, it's gonna ask you "Do you want
to contribute?" And then from there,
it's creating the scenario in your own
GitHub account and then raising a PR
to the catalog backend, where initially
our GitHub Copilot is gonna review, and
then one of our V team admins will look
into the scenario and accepting it.
So all that to switch to my next demo,
where I'm gonna show you what it takes to
clone the repo, use the agents, and then
obviously walking you through the basics
of creating your own custom scenario.
So I'm inside the trainer demo
deploy repo that I cloned from
GitHub, and I'll walk you through
a bit what the agents are about.
So if you're a little bit familiar
with how agents are working today,
it's typically a markdown file,
maybe prompt files and skills.
So I'm following GitHub Copilot as
our AI assistant platform, which
means we have our .github folder.
Underneath you have the agents, and then
down here we have prompts and skills.
And then workflows is just the
traditional GitHub actions pipelines.
For this scenario, as I mentioned in the
presentation, we created a collection
of GitHub Copilot agentic scenario, and
it's literally following eight steps.
So the starting point, and mainly I
would say the only agent you would
actually rely on is the conductor
or the scenario orchestrator.
You kick off with a prompt,
and I'll show you a few to just
speed up the demo a little bit.
What does it actually mean to
create a new custom scenario?
And then I might kick off one
of them live, but then switching
back to an already created one.
So when you run the conductor
orchestrator, it's gonna hand over to
any of the other ones whenever needed.
It's gonna run a validation step.
So if I open up the file, like
everything here is plain markdown.
You can customize this, modify this, and
then again, why not contributing to it?
So not gonna bore you with reading
through everything that we have
here, but as you can see, it's just
following traditional markdown, and
you create instructions like do this,
do that, this is what it's allowed,
this is what's not allowed, and so on.
So we start with running a prompt.
So let me open up my Copilot,
and I'm gonna ask to help me
Generate my next demo scenario using
an Azure App Service single region
connecting to a storage account, maybe
the one we already used before, right?
Add a few images into the blob storage
and present them in a web page.
Pretty easy, pretty straightforward.
You could make this as easy,
as complex as you want.
But the whole idea here is that we want an
Azure App Service connecting to storage.
Now, what I mean by be as high level or
specific as possible, I could say, "Don't
use storage account keys, but rely on RBAC
managed identity permissions." Just to
give you an example, like what is possible
When you kick it off, I started with
the conductor, and it's basically gonna
loop through the different scenarios.
It's coming up with its own name,
like App Service Blob Gallery.
I think it's fine.
And that folder is then getting
created in the generated scenarios.
That's like hard-coded location and the
new folder App Service Blob Gallery.
Since it recognizes an application
layer, it's gonna ask, "Do
you want a sample web app?
And if so, do you want it pretty
generic, or do you want it for a specific
industry?" So let's obviously say yes
because, again, thinking about the purpose
or the main starting point, do functional
demos, you can talk about Azure web apps,
obviously, but it's still cooler, I think,
if you can add an actual workload to it.
So I'm gonna say yes, and let's
do real estate as industry.
While it's spinning up here, let me
walk you through the rest of the flow.
So it's gonna architect a solution,
like looking at… I was already pretty
specific, like I want a web app and
storage, but you could actually flip
it around and providing an actual
functional scenario where then you rely
on the agentic information to come up
with a potential reference architecture.
Once you have the architecture done,
you need to approve it, you need
to validate, and from there it's
gonna create a couple of diagrams.
I'll show you that for an
already created scenario.
After that, it's gonna create the Bicep
templates using the modular approach
that I mentioned, developing the actual
web app scenario, running the deployment
into your Azure subscription using AZD,
the same demo piece would be viable here
that I showed you at the start of the
presentation, creating the demo guide,
and then last, suggesting to contribute.
As you can see here,
it's nicely moving on.
It's already at step number two.
I'm not gonna wait for this.
I'm gonna switch to an already
created scenario because otherwise
it would take fifteen, thirty
minutes, sometimes close to an hour.
So I'm gonna use about the same
Example, but slightly different.
So I didn't specify
anything really detailed.
I just ran a prompt, "Help me
build a demo scenario for Azure
App Service connecting to Cosmos
Database." It created the folder.
It asked for the industry specifics,
where I defined healthcare I confirmed,
and then as you can see here, it took
a little bit of time, but this is not
a hundred percent correct because I
started this I think two days ago and
then closing the laptop overnight, so
it was not running the whole night.
But if you think about the topic of
the session, running deployments while
you're sleeping, this is basically
one of those possibilities, right?
Zooming in on all the details, it's
gonna loop through each and every step.
We have step number one, then moving
on to step number two, defining the
architecture, creating the diagrams,
more diagrams, running the deployment.
All tests are done, all successful
deployments succeeded, and
eventually we get the link.
A bit more detailed, what we get in
our repo is an application service
folder with everything that we need.
This is like the full artifacts list We
have the demo guide markdown, including
screenshots live from the Azure portal.
We have our infra folder with the
Azure Bicep files, the sample source
application for our healthcare,
and the different diagrams.
Let me pull up a diagram to give you
some idea, like what is this actually
creating There's a overall architecture
diagram, then there's the runtime,
so typically the back end and what
the user flow within the application
you could say looks like We're done.
We ran the deployment.
So if I switch back to my Azure
environment, I got my application Cosmos.
What you're gonna see here is that it's
deploying a lot more because behind the
scenes we already provide instructions to
the agent to also bring in best practices
around security, best practices around
high availability, and that's one of
those hundred and something steps that
I showed you in the chat conversation.
If I down navigate to my application
You can see here that we have a dashboard
for healthcare operations, and this
is what I mean by it's immediately
functional for that specific industry.
I can look into details, and it's
like a full functional web application
Out of the box, high available,
everything that you need.
And obviously the whole main
goal, it's not about the app,
it's about what the app can do.
So for example, here, if I move back
to my Azure environment, it brought
in a concept of high availability
deployment slots, so it has two of them.
There's already monitoring integrated, so
you can talk about monitoring, navigating
across the site, and then seeing all the
telemetry using Application Insights.
Following best practices, I'm not
using key-based authentication, but if
so, it's gonna use Key Vault because
I didn't explicitly ask for it.
And then the connectivity from
the app to the Cosmos database
is using private endpoints, like
no public connectivity possible.
There's a lot more you can do with
this, but I hope this short example
gives you some idea about really
starting to build your own demos.
And then before I close out, let
me go back to the scenario where
then all the way at the end, it
actually asked for contribution.
I confirmed OK to contribute, and what
it does is then moving all the artifacts,
the demo guide, the template, everything
that we need, the sample app, into
your individual GitHub account, and
then contributing to the main catalog.
So if I then go back to the catalog, and
I would filter on healthcare, you can
see that right now there's nothing in
here because it still has the filter.
But this nice scenario is
already available, and that's
mainly what it's all about.
That's pretty much it on using Azure
AI, our trainer demo deploy static
catalog, maybe moving into the agentic
scenario from here, contributing,
helping, feeding that catalog.
That's the whole idea.
But most important, if you skip
the catalog and you wanna use it
to just build your own demo/Azure
testing scenarios, I hope you're
gonna enjoy our agentic scenario.
So with that, let's switch back to the
presentation and wrap it up from here.
Good.
We're almost there, but I wanna
emphasize again this last piece, and
that's where you come in knowing that
you can actually contribute to the
success of this open source platform.
Now, what this means is, remember,
first of all, it's 100% open source.
You can contribute in any possible way.
You can start from the existing
static scenarios in the catalog,
reviewing them, deploying them,
testing them, and providing feedback.
You can use the agentic approach, create
your own custom scenario, a single one,
multi ones, depending on how many demo
scenarios you have in mind, and then
from there, contributing them back.
Maybe you're not that familiar with
AZD, maybe you're not familiar with
scenarios, or maybe you deploy a
scenario, you find optimizations
for the demo guides, the demo steps,
then again, you can contribute.
So it's open source.
Anyone can use it, and I would
like to see some of your scenarios
coming in the near future.
So with that, I'm gonna wrap it up.
I already want to thank you
for watching my session.
Thank you so much for being here.
I hope you enjoy the rest of the
conference, and again, never hesitate
reaching out regarding the session.
If you're using our platform,
please let us know if you like it.
By the way, there's that feedback
link inside the platform itself,
and hope to see you again in
any of the future sessions here.
Thank you so much, and
enjoy the rest of the day.